masbukti.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy - Masbukti.com

_This document was last updated on Febrary 02, 2017_

### GENERAL

**PURPOSE OF POLICY**

http://masbukti.com (“us”, “we”, “the Site”) undertakes to respect the privacy rights of every visitors, users and others who use [http://masbukti.com](http://masbukti.com/). Accordingly, we have developed the current privacy policy to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices. It explains how http://masbukti.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from the visitors of the Site. The following outlines our privacy policy:

###  INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

**WHAT BASIC INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT?**

The Site can collect personal information from you in two situations. The first is if you should contact us via the “contact us” page. In this situation, you should provide us with your name and email address. The second is if you want to leave a comment to the posts during which you may be asked for a name and other information. 

**WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT?**

AUTOMATIC COLLECTION: When you visit to http://masbukti.com, the servers will automatically track basic information about your interaction with our website as well as information that your web browser sends. Such log information includes, but is not limited to, the details of the browser, IP addresses, timestamps, referring pages, the address of the website you visited before you came to http://masbukti.com, the data about your operation system and language. Any of such information cannot personally determine concrete visitors to this site. This kind of information is traced for routine management and maintenance.

COOKIES. Cookies are used to store your personal information while you are on the site and this also incresaes the security. This doesn't take much of your time as only one pop-up launches every time you come to the website. Some third party advertisements are also used to support our website http://masbukti.com financially. Some advertisers may also use different technologies such as cookies and web beacons while they advertise on our site . This also sends these advertisers(such as Google through the Google AdSense account) some information which includes your IP, ISP and the version and name of the browser you've installed, and in some cases, the version of flash you've installed. The purpose of this is to achieve geotargeting (showing London real estate ads to someone in London, for example) or to show specific ads such as showing sports ads to someone who frequently visits sports websites.

DoubleClick COOKIES. Cookies can also be used for ad serving through Google DoubleClick which stores a cookie on your PC while you are browsing a website and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (this may also include some of the Google AdSense advertisements). Interest based targeting can also be enable through cookies which shows specific ads to you according to your preferences. Ads shown to you will be based on your previous browsing history so that only relevant ads are shown to you. (For example, if you have been visiting cooking sites, you may visit a cooking website while visiting a non-relevant site such as a sports website). It is to be made sure that it does NOT track your personal information such as your name, email address, physicall address, IP address, telephone number, social security number, bank accoutn number or credit card number etc. You also have the option to opt out of this ad-serving on all the sites using the link http://www.google.com/doubleclick/ . Here you can choose to disable or selectively turn on off your cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings. Also this is the page you should visit to set any preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. In short, this affects how you interact with our site as well as the other sites. This may also include the inability to login to service programs, such as logging into forums and accounts. However, it is also to be remembered that deleting cookies will not allow you to permanently opt out of any advertising programs.

### WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

From time-to-time, the Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit those websites, it is important to understand our privacy practices and terms of use do not extend to those sites. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their practices.

### POLICY UPDATES AND CONTACT INFORMATION

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

http://masbukti.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://masbukti.com/terms_of_use). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS**

If you have questions or comments about masbukti.com’s privacy policy, contact us by sending email to rustampaskaev84@gmail.com. We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to every one.

Thank you for choosing masbukti.com!
